risk t r
RIS Time Magazine is in the news which
is rare for a magazine these days they
ran a list of the top 10 risks and
threats facing the world this year for
instance watch out for Isis in 2016 good
reporting Time
Magazine you got more Scoops than the
Baskin Robins they also list China and a
closed Europe so I have to say overall
there's some pretty boring risks risk
should be risky like getting your balls
wax the Fantastic
Sams got to be the
hair uh comedians I want you to give me
as many actual risks for 2016 as you can
I'm going to put 60 seconds on the clock
and begin Jonah Courtney Love becomes
eligible for the Rock and Roll Hall of
Fame I
know points um Michaela uh I might never
be a member of Taylor Swiss squad points
I'm sorry yeah Doug True Detective three
points Doug Amanda binds reappears
Caesar Shadow six more weeks of winter
yes
boys Jonah I'm at risk of accidentally
telling people that dies a new Star Wars
oh my God I did it oh my go is there a
crazy ass spoiler oh hey if you haven't
seen it yet
you you know
what the movie's been out for weeks it's
made almost a billion dollars
catch up or shut
up